moviecorner.com 2017-06-26

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated: **January 4, 2017**

* * *

At Findinfo "FI", we respect your privacy, and we understand the importance of the information you entrust to us. This Privacy Policy describes the practices concerning the information collected by the Findinfo family of companies consisting of Findinfo, Ltd ("Findinfo", "we", "us" and "our") through the use of the (i) websites and applications, e.g. content, products, forums and services, controlled by Findinfo, Ltd. (the "FI Products") and (ii) our "Search Applications" made available by means of a search box on a FI Product or website from which you can access our search services. These Search Applications are controlled by Findinfo, Ltd. Collectively, we refer to the FI Products and these Search Applications in this Privacy Policy as the "FI Services".

Findinfo respects the privacy of users of the FI Services, and has developed this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of the FI Services, the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. Unless indicated otherwise FI Services are subject to our [Terms of Service](http://find.info/tos/), this [Privacy Policy](http://find.info/privacypolicy/), and for downloadable software (where applicable) the [End User License Agreement](http://find.info/eula/); Certain FI Services may be subject to different privacy policies and/or terms of service as indicated on the sites from where those services are available and/ or accessed.

A. Search services

The Search Applications provide features to facilitate Internet search and communication services using the FI Products including through the MyWay and MyWebSearch portals and email. This search functionality may be implemented through browser settings and "extensions" that set or default your browser homepage, start page, new tab page and/or default search setting(s), depending on which FI Product you are using and what options you select. We may provide you a way to decline or opt-out of the setting(s) change by unchecking the appropriate checkbox during the download and installation process for the relevant FI Product that provides access to the Search Applications. Certain FI Products, such as Chrome new tab products, may be available through the online store operated by the browser developer (e.g., the Chrome web store) and the user disclosures and options may vary based on the store’s requirements. The search features, as well as other non-search-related features, may be customized by you. In addition, you may be able to disable or remove the default search features by removing or disabling the applicable files you downloaded from the FI Products, or changing your default search within your browser, depending on your browser, browser version, and tools and features provided in your respective browser.

B. Information we collect

We may collect information from you that may identify you, such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number and anonymous Information, such as the number of your page views, link clicks, and login times. Your information may be kept in an identifiable format, or in an aggregate format which means that you cannot reasonably be identified from it.

C. How we collect information

We use various technologies to collect information from your device and about your activities on the FI Services:

  1. Information You Provide To Us. We may collect and store any information you provide when using the FI Services (e.g. when registering on the MyWay Site) or that you provide in some other manner. This information may include your name, email address, telephone number, username and password or information provided when you log-in to the FI Services via Facebook or any other social media site (you should review the privacy policy of Facebook or any other social media site through which you choose to log into certain FI Services). We also collect and store information and other content you post to the FI Services, where such features are made available (e.g., MyScrapNook). When we provide you with an email inbox as part of an FI Product, we may monitor and collect the contents of such emails in the course of normal maintenance of the relevant FI Product and its systems. Further, in order to permit us to protect the quality of our products and services, we may to the extent permitted by applicable law access your account and records on a case by case basis to investigate complaints or other allegations.
  2. Automatically Captured Information. We automatically collect information from your computer and/or device when you use the FI Services. This information may include your IP address, your browser type and language and other browser-related information, a time-stamp, the keyword query, search query text, search results clicked, pages viewed, search history, the content of any of our undeleted cookies, including a unique identifier (see [section D](http://find.info/privacypolicy/#cookies) on "Cookies" below), software installed upon and/or devices connected to your computer and/or device, and the referring website address.
  3. Other Technologies. We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons, cookies and other similar technologies, to track your use of the FI Services (see our cookies policy). Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of sites. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer as part of the FI Services for our users.
  4. Information Collected By Third-Parties And Behavioral Advertising.

On The FI Services: We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements or place ad tags or beacons on or via FI Services. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. (To learn more about cookies generally, please go to our [Cookies policy](http://find.info/cookies/). This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and evaluate its effectiveness. We may also use information collected by these third-parties to better understand our own users, their interests, how they use our products, improve and customize our products, and to deliver ads targeted to you (either on our FI Services or on other websites whether or not owned and operated by us). Please note, some of these third-party advertising companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, or the Digital Advertising Alliance, each of which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies. For more information about limiting third-party advertising cookies, please visit the following links: [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), [youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/), or [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

On Third Party Sites, Services And Applications. Findinfo and its affiliates work with various companies, such as advertisers, ad networks and data management platforms, that may help us and other companies to tailor online ads, including through behavioral advertising designed to target users’ interests and deliver more relevant advertising. To provide such ads, these third parties may collect and/or we may disclose to these third parties a unique ID that may be associated with your device’s platform or a device/internet browser combination, or they may tell us based on their own data, if that unique ID is associated with a particular segment (such as a reality show watcher falling within a certain demographic (e.g. female aged 30 – 40)).

We or these third parties may collect the following information (and similar information):

    * Demographic data collected on FI Services (e.g., age, zip or postal code, gender) and geographic location derived from your IP address on your visits to, and collected on, the FI Services and non-affiliated websites and applications;
    * Data about your use of or visits to the FI Services and non-affiliated websites and applications; 
    * Data on your interaction with the advertisement displayed on third party websites and applications; and 
    * Interest and usage data (such as the pages you view and links you click on) acquired from other companies. 
    * We may disclose any or all of the collected information to third parties. 

We or these third parties may use the collected information to provide advertisements of interest to you on certain FI Services and non-affiliated websites and applications and for other purposes described in this privacy policy (such as to improve or customize our products). Three companies we currently work with to target our own ads on other websites based on activity on the FI Services are AppNexus, Adobe and Exelate. If you tell us not to send you these types of ads by opting out (as described [below](http://find.info/privacypolicy/#cookies)), you may still see our ads on other companies’ websites, but they will not be specifically tailored to you based on your activity on our FI Services.

To learn about – and if you would like to, opt-out of targeted advertising from -- various types of ad networks that we may work with, and who are involved in serving online behavioral advertising, please go to www.aboutads.info/choices, www.networkadvertising.org and/or www.youronlinechoices.com and opt-out of online behavioral advertising.

  5. Please note that you cannot opt-out of ads on mobile apps via the site listed above. However, your mobile devices may offer settings that enable users to limit how mobile device ad tracking occurs, using unique device identifiers such as the Apple IDFA and Google Android Advertising ID. Some information about those settings may be reviewed for Apple [here](http://support.apple.com/kb/HT4228) and for Android [here](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en).
  6. Do not track signals. FI Services systems are not configured to respond to Web browser "do not track" signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across third-party Web sites or online services.

D. Cookies

We use cookies and similar technologies (such as local stored objects) to collect and store information when you interact with the FI Services, such as when you use our web and search tools and extensions, view our emails or view our ads. We, and certain third parties we work with e.g. ad networks and data management platforms, may also use these technologies to better target ads to you based on your online browsing activities. Please see our [Cookies Policy](http://find.info/cookies/index.html) for further information about our use of these technologies, and please see the above Section titled "[On Third Party Sites, Services and Applications](http://find.info/privacypolicy/#tsa)" to learn more about how we use information to (and work with others that use information to) provide behavioral targeted advertising. 

Major browsers provide users with various options when it comes to cookies. Users can usually set their browsers to block all third-party cookies (which are those set by third-party companies collecting information on websites operated by other companies), block all cookies (including first-party cookies such as the ones Findinfo uses to collect search activity information about its users), or block specific cookies. To modify your cookie settings, please refer to the following support pages for each browser you use to access the Website:

  * Internet Explorer help: <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-gb/windows7/how-to-manage-cookies-in-internet-explorer-9>
  * Firefox help: <http://kb.mozillazine.org/Cookies#Firefox>
  * Safari help: <http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042>
  * Chrome help: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en>

E. How We Use The Information We Collect

We may use information that we collect about you to: 

  * Deliver the products and services that you have requested;
  * Respond to your queries with the best possible answers and search results;
  * Provide you with customer support;
  * Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * Communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone, display media and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, Findinfo affiliates or other third parties;
  * Enable us and our search and advertising partners to develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests, when you use the FI Services, other websites and services, or mobile applications;
  * Verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;
  * Enforce our terms and conditions;
  * Manage our business and protect the quality of the FI Services, which includes maintenance of the FI Services systems;
  * Investigate complaints, abuse or other allegations; and
  * Perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

F. With Whom We Share Your Information

We share your information with others as indicated below: 

  1. Authorized service providers: We may share your information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include providing customer service, technical and operational support, email services, and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, billing and payment processing (if we ever accept payments from our users), supporting our FI Services functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our FI Services, as well as when we have notified you, or you have requested, that we do so. These service providers may have access to information, which is needed to perform their functions.
  2. Advertisers and Ad Networks: As described above under "Information Collected By Third Parties and Behavioral Advertising", third party advertisers and ad networks, data management platforms, and other third parties may collect information themselves from the FI Services and/or we may provide them with the information described above for purposes of delivering relevant ads.
  3. Business partners: When you engage in promotions offered through the FI Services, we may share information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.
  4. Other IAC businesses. We are part of the IAC family of businesses (www.iac.com). We may share information we collect with our affiliated IAC companies. Sharing information with our IAC affiliates enables us to provide you with information about a variety of products and services that might interest you.
  5. Share with a friend/product specific features. We share information with your friends where you use the "share with the friend functionality" on some of our FI Services (for example you can use MyFunCards to send a customized e-card to your friends).
  6. Other Situations. We may disclose your information (i) in good faith compliance with a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency, (ii) in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; (iii) to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; (iv) to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; (v) to enforce our FI Services terms and conditions or other agreements or policies; and (vi) in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business or the FI Services (or a majority of the assets of either), a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. In addition, we may share aggregated information we collect, under any of the above circumstances, with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis.

G. Where Will We Store Your Information?

Information we collect, or permit third parties such as advertising companies and advertising networks to collect using cookies, beacons, pixels and similar technology, may be transferred to, stored and processed outside your country of residence in any country or territory where one or more of our affiliated group companies, third party service providers or advertising companies or advertising networks are located or maintain facilities, including but not limited to the United States and Ireland.

While other territories may not have the same standards of data protection as those within your home country, we will continue to protect the information transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By using the FI Services you consent to the transfer of your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy.

H. Third-Party Websites

There may be places in the FI Services where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy policy of all third-party websites you visit.

I. Your Choices About Collection And Use Of Your Information

You may tell us not to share your information with third parties or the Findinfo companies for direct marketing purposes by clicking on the following link and entering the email address associated with your account: [support@find.info](mailto:support@find.info). Please note, if you do not allow us to collect information from you it may result in you being unable to use certain features of the FI Services; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our FI Services.

Please see our [Cookies Policy](http://find.info/cookies/index.html) for further information about our use of these technologies and how you can opt out of cookies.

J. How To Edit, Delete Or Access Your Information

You may have the right to ask for a copy of certain information that we hold about you in our records, to correct any inaccuracies and to update any out-of-date information. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, or wish to object to our use of your information, please write to us at the address listed below.

Please note that in some countries we may be permitted to charge a fee specified by law for providing you with copies of information we may hold about you.

K. How We Protect Your Information

The security and confidentiality of you information is very important to us, thus we take certain security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your information from unauthorized access and disclosure. Please know that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any password you may use to access the FI Services, and agree not to transfer your user name or password, or lend or otherwise transfer your use of or access to the FI Services, to any third party. You are fully responsible for all activity that occurs in connection with your user name or password. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your user name or password or any other breach of security related to your account or the FI Services, and to ensure that you "log off"/exit from your account (if applicable) at the end of each session. We are not liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with any of the foregoing obligations.

L. Requests To Remove Search Results Pursuant To European Court Of Justice Ruling

Following a recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (ECJ), users of our European web search and reference services who are EU residents may request that certain results do not appear following a web search for the user’s name.

If you would like to request the removal of a search result generated using your name as the search term, please send your request in writing to IAC Search and Media Europe, Ltd at the address below. To assist us in processing your request in timely manner, please make your request in English if you are able to do so. Your request should include any information relevant to your request, including: (i) your name, email and postal address; (ii) the URL (i.e., "web address") for each link that you are requesting to be removed; (iii) a brief explanation of why you believe such results should be removed; (iv) an explanation of whether or not you fulfil a role in public life; and (v) an explanation as to why the contents of the link you wish to have removed relate to you.

To help us prevent fraudulent removal requests, please also include a legible copy of a document that verifies your identity. You need not provide a government-issued document; a utility bill or similar mailing will suffice. You may also obscure parts of the document such as identifying numbers so long as the document continues to clearly identify you. If you are requesting the removal of search results that contain photographs of you, please ensure that the identifying document includes your photograph. If you are making the request on behalf of another person, please indicate your relationship to that person and provide evidence of your authority to make such request. All requests for removal will be reviewed by IAC Search and Media Europe Limited’s legal and compliance team in Ireland and we reserve the right, in compliance with applicable laws and considering the balance between the user’s right to privacy and the public’s interest in access to information, to accept or reject, or make further inquiries regarding, any requests.

M. Children's Privacy

Our FI Services are intended for general audiences over the age of 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 years old. If you are not over 13 years old, **_DO NOT DOWNLOAD OR USE THE FI SERVICES_**.

N. No Rights Of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any information relating to users of the FI Services.

O. Changes To This Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your information, we will notify you by posting notice of the changes on or through the applicable FI Services, or notifying you of these changes in another way reasonably calculated to provide notice. We recommend that you check this page, the help menu within an FI Product, from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

We may acquire or develop new FI Products and/or FI Services from time to time that require additional privacy disclosure. In such case, we will add these additional provisions in a product specific annex or section that will only apply to such new FI Product or FI Service and will not vary the terms of this Privacy Policy in relation to your use of existing FI Products and FI Services (and, as such, we will not be required to notify you of such additional terms unless you also use the new FI Products or FI Services).

P. Your California Privacy Rights

Under the California "Shine The Light" law, California residents may opt-out of the disclosure of information to third parties for direct marketing purposes (as those concepts are defined in that law) However, we do not currently engage in the type of sharing covered by that law.

Q. How To Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or wish to review, amend or delete any information we are storing, please contact us by email or postal mail at: 

END OF DOCUMENT.

©2020Findinfo, Ltd.® All rights reserved.
